http://www.wincustomize.com/privacy

Latest News
Berlin startup company, Wonder, raises $11 million for new video conferencing program
Wednesday,
1:00 PM
by
Tatiora
Discussion:
Personal Computing
Get Your Desktop Ready for Christmas!
Tuesday,
12:49 PM
by
Island Dog
Discussion:
WinCustomize News
Fun with Fences: Using Fences on Multiple Monitors
Thursday,
1:00 PM
by
Tatiora
Discussion:
Stardock Blog
WinCustomize Monthly Wrap-up - November Edition
Tuesday,
9:17 AM
by
Island Dog
Discussion:
WinCustomize News
Revisiting a Christmas Skinning Classic....ChristmasTime
Friday,
1:00 PM
by
Island Dog
Discussion:
Essential Articles
Misc.
View Homepage
Return to the WinCustomize homepage.
Save
CursorFX is a utility which allows you to have much more flexibility in the cursors
you use to interact with Windows. CursorFX users can create and use cursors that
look and feel far superior to anything you've ever seen before! Best of all, it's
really easy to create your own super-charged cursors!
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Object Desktop
Website |
Download
| Purchase
Customize Windows with additional styles beyond light and dark mode
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Object Desktop
Website
| Download
| Purchase
Stardock DeskScapes extends Windows 10 with the ability to run spectacular animated wallpapers (Dreams) on your desktop.
Choose your Dream from our extensive library to personalize your pc.
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Object Desktop
Website |
Download
| Purchase
IconPackager is a program that allows users to change nearly all of their Windows
icons at once by applying "packages" of icons. A package of icons contains
icons to replace most of the common icons on your Windows PC.
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Icons
Icons for applications and folders.
Rainmeter allows you to display customizable skins on your desktop, from hardware usage meters to fully functional audio visualizers.
You are only limited by your imagination and creativity.
Rainmeter is open source software distributed free of charge under the terms of the GNU GPL v2 license.
Website | Download
Show off your favorite desktop configuration by uploading a screenshot of your desktop!
SoundPackager brings customization of your auditory experience to Object Desktop!
Users can now choose from "sound packages" to enhance their Windows desktop
experience. Over 30 different system sounds are supported; unique new Stardock Design
sound packages are included with the package.
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Purchase
Microsoft Windows® 8 is shipped without the "Start" menu. Stardock heard the cries from Windows 8
users. We put the "Start" menu back in Windows 8. We accurately recreated the most used desktop
feature billions of users depend on every day and packed it with additional functionality.
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Object Desktop
Website |
Download
| Purchase
The finest collection of desktop backgrounds on the Internet!
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Object Desktop
WindowBlinds changes the look and feel of your Windows desktop by applying visual
styles to your entire Windows environment. When a visual style is applied, they
change nearly every elements of the Windows GUI such as title bars, push buttons,
the Start bar, menu and more.
Publisher:
Stardock Corporation
Developer:
Stardock Corporation
Genre:
Purchase
Winstep Extreme is a powerful suite of applications that merge incredible usability and performance with breathtaking eye candy. Add your own Menus, Docks, Tabbed Docks, Taskbar and Widgets with this Windows User Interface Replacement!
Website | Download
View Gallery List
View a list of all of the different galleries available in WinCustomize, which you
can then browse individually.
Explore All
Explore all available galleries on WinCustomize.
Customize This Menu
This option is only available for subscribers of WinCustomize. If you are a subscriber
it will allow you to select which categories you would like to see in this menu
from a list of all galleries available on the site. This information will be stored
on your account for all your future visits.
Subscribe
Articles
Berlin startup company, Wonder, raises $11 million...
Get Your Desktop Ready for Christmas!
Fun with Fences: Using Fences on Multiple Monitors
WinCustomize Monthly Wrap-up - November Edition
Revisiting a Christmas Skinning Classic....Christm...
Fences: Making Desktop Customization Work for YOU
WC Community Question: Roasted, Fried, or Smoked T...
Happy Thanksgiving Week, WinCustomize!
Changing Windows System Sounds with SoundPackager
WC Community Question: Desktop, Laptop, or Both?
View Articles Page
Tutorials
Forums
Dreamweaver needs to be excluded
Blur behind titlebar
Dubtech...could be a style.
Screen blur
Changing Windows 10 Icons with IconPackager 10
glitches on title text
Remember IconX? Let's check it out!
Fun with Fences: Using Fences on Multiple Monitors
So starkers Gets Himself Mobility Scooter
Standard Fences for Users
View Forums
Shop
Upload
View Cart
Privacy Policy
Stardock.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: Stardock.com This policy is also applicable to Stardock's other Web sites, including but not limited to: Stardock.net, WinCustomize.com, JoeUser.com, Windowblinds.net, DesktopX.net, GalCiv.com, PoliticalMachine.com, and ObjectDesktop.net.
WE DO NOT SHARE YOUR EMAIL ADDRESSES OR PERSONAL INFORMATION WITH ANYONE.
Information Automatically Logged
We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer our Web site. This information is used to generate reports on the overall traffic to the site for bandwidth planning and usage statistics.
Stardock Activation
Beginning in 2005, some Stardock products require activation over the Internet to use their enhanced versions. Depending on if your order was directly through Stardock or through a third-party, we may ask for your first name, last name, email address, and the serial number/activation code for the product you have purchased.
Your IP address and number of activation attempts will also be logged. There are reasonable limits on how often you can activate a given product to help deter piracy, but for most users, this limit will not be reached. If you have difficulties, please contact support@stardock.com. This information will not be used by third parties, but may be used by Stardock to contact you about updates or other Stardock-related news.
Cookies
Our Site uses cookies to keep track of items in your shopping cart. Stardock.net accounts on the various websites (like WinCustomize.com and for installing software via Stardock Central) also uses cookies as part of their validation process.
Advertisers
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. While we use cookies in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.
Some customer data is shared with the advertising companies (i.e. ONLY what they have access to from setting in your cookies). We do not allow advertisers to see any private information including email addresses, home addresses, phone numbers, or any other private information.
Registration Forms
Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email) and demographic information (like their zip code and age).
Contact information from the registration forms is used to get in touch with the customer when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site. We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Order Forms
Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services. We collect contact information (like their email address), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code and age).
Contact information from the order forms is used to ship purchases, information about our company. The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to bill the user for products and services.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We may use this data in the future to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Surveys
Our online surveys ask visitors for demographic information (like zip code or age).
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data in the future to tailor our visitor's experience at our site showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
Email
Stardock scans the text of e-mail messages in order to filter spam and detect viruses.
This process is completely automated and involves no humans.
The only exception includes requests by users that Wincustomize support staff access their email messages in order to diagnose problems; when Stardock is required by law to do so; and when we are compelled to view or disclose personal information because we reasonably believe it's necessary in order to protect the rights, property or safety of Stardock, its users and the public. Stardock only scans e-mail contents to provide you a reliable service. Stardock does not share or reveal e-mail content or personal information with third parties, other than in certain exceptions dictated by the law and common sense.
Assessments (Hardware)
Stardock's TweakVista and Tweak7 products, at the request of the user, send generic information about the computer hardware under analysis to Stardock.
This data will not be provided to any third parties and will only be used to provide anonymous high level reports to other customers of TweakVista and Tweak7.
External Links
This site contains links to other sites. Stardock.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.
Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.
Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Credit card information for orders is secured via industry standard 128-bit SSL encryption.
Choice/Opt-Out
Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving promotional/marketing information from us via Stardock Magazine.
You can send email to info@stardock.com
You can visit the following URL: https://www.stardock.com/accounts/subscriptions
In addition, our MyColors products may prompt you for additional opt-in decisions during check out through our online store.  These questions will default to opting-out of additional promotional communications from our affiliates, however customers may choose to receive promotional e-mails at their discretion.
Data Quality/Access
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:
You can send email to sales@stardock.com
Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: info@stardock.com
Home |
About |
Privacy |
Upload Guidelines |
Terms of Service |
Help
Copyright ©
Stardock Corporation. All Rights Reserved.
web-wc01
